At point 1 the resistance of the lamp filament (in Ω) is   
 
    100.  
 
 At point 2 the resistance of the lamp filament (in Ω) is   
 
    150.  
 
 The curve does not obey Ohms law since a doubling of voltage from 60 V to 120 V does not result in a corresponding doubling of current. That is, the resistance i 
      s not constant-it increases at higher currents due to a heating effect                                                                                       
 